<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Socialization</string>
    <string name="title_age_detail">Age Detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>

    <string name="aboutTeacher">
        Thank you to my teacher Mr. Sharpe
        I am beyond thankful to spend one semester you.
        I have acquired a tremendous amount of knowledge from you that I will take with me on my journey through life.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutParents">
        Thank you to my wonderful parents. I could never ask more out of you. I love you mom and dad.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutGirlfriend">
        Thank you to my girlfriend♥ You are truly everything I could ever ask for.
        You motivate me, make me laugh, and still give me butterflies.
        I have created so many memories with you I will never forget.
    </string>

    <string name="sociologist_preference_key">sociologistPrefKey</string>
    <string name="sociologist_data_key">sociologistDataKey</string>

    <!--Details for age groups-->

    <string name="erickson0">
        Basic biological needs are met. Emotional and physical bonds between baby and parent.
    </string>

    <string name="erickson1">
        Self control of behavior and body functions occurs. Behaviors that are socially acceptable are learned and they wish to abide by
    </string>

    <string name="erickson2">
        Imagination starts to develop. Language improves. Has a self-image of ones self
    </string>

    <string name="erickson3">
        Kids learn to complete tasks. Learn to share and play nicely.
    </string>

    <string name="erickson4">
        Child develops self-identity. Time of rebellion and question.
    </string>

    <string name="erickson5">
        Risktaking entering into a caring and loving state.
    </string>

    <string name="erickson6">
        Adult needs to contribute back to his or her world
    </string>

    <string name="erickson7">
        Able to look back on the past and feel a sens of accomplishment based on what they feel is important
    </string>


    <string name="piaget0">
        Child spends time on sensation and movement.
        Learning requires motor response that is converted to pleasurable sensation.
        Object permanence at 10 months.
    </string>

    <string name="piaget1">
        Children are not yet able to fully function in society.
        Vocabulary expands greatly.
        Reversibility not yet functioning.
        Unable to see from someone elses point of view.
    </string>

    <string name="piaget2">
        Object permanence, conversation and reversibility are fully operational.
        World and its values are seen in black and white. Very hard to understand grey issues.
    </string>

    <string name="piaget3">
        Has ability to think symbolicly. Truth, justice, personal rights and freedom. Altruistic.
        Not everyone gets to this stage.
    </string>


    <string name="kohlberg0">
        Moral behavior is determined by parents.
        Cannot grasp right and wrong.
        They only understand punishments and rewards.
        Very self centered.
    </string>

    <string name="kohlberg1">
        In the beginning children need the approval of others.
        Then children learn how to interact under certain social conditioning.
        Child now begins to judge why people do what they do.
        Many adults do not go beyond this stage.
    </string>

    <string name="kohlberg2">
        Morality drives their action.
        Personal ethics drive one\'s actions.
        Concerned with the rights of others.
        Very few truly reach this stage.
    </string>

</resources>
